http://www.holdmyrod.com/index.php/privacy/

HoldMyRod Simplify your fishing experience.
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.holdmyrod.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via phone at (30767-31105) or by using the contact form on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Compliance With Children's Online Privacy ActHoldMyRod.com does not knowingly collect the personal information of persons under the age of 18. If we learn of any personal information collected from persons under the age of 18, it will be immediately deleted.
CookiesMany websites use cookies, small text files on your hard drive that are accesible only to the site that placed it on your hard drive. The data collected from cookies helps a website determine how many people visit the site and how many pages they view. You can set your web browser to warn you before you accept a cookie. When visiting our websites, we may use cookies on some pages simply to help us serve you better each time you return.
SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via our website Contact form.
Rod Holders
T-Shirts
Accessories
Photo Gallery
Blog
Our Story
Resources
Contact
©2020 HoldMyRod.com. All Rights Reserved.
